<GameFile name="Klondike">
	
	<Board>
		<Deck numDecks="1" />
		<Rules>
		<![CDATA[
		   <b>Klondike Solitaire Rules</b>
				<br><br> (From Wikipedia) Taking a shuffled standard 52-card deck of playing cards (without Jokers),
				one upturned card is dealt on the left of the playing area, then six downturned cards
				(from left to right).<p> On top of the downturned cards, an upturned card is dealt on the 
				left-most downturned pile, and downturned cards on the rest until all piles have an 
				upturned card. The piles should look like the figure to the right.<p>The four foundations 
				(light rectangles in the upper right of the figure) are built up by suit from Ace 
				(low in this game) to King, and the tableau piles can be built down by alternate colors,
				and partial or complete piles can be moved if they are built down by alternate colors also. 
				Any empty piles can be filled with a King or a pile of cards with a King.<p> The point of 
				the game is to build up a stack of cards starting with 2 and ending with King, all of 
				the same suit. Once this is accomplished, the goal is to move this to a foundation, 
				where the player has previously placed the Ace of that suit. Once the player has done this, 
				they will have \finished\ that suit- the goal being, of course, to finish all suits, 
				at which time the player will have won.<br><br><b> Scoring </b><br><br>
				Moving cards directly from the Waste stack to a Foundation awards 10 points. However, 
				if the card is first moved to a Tableau, and then to a Foundation, then an extra 5 points 
				are received for a total of 15. Thus in order to receive a maximum score, no cards should be moved 
				directly from the Waste to Foundation.<p>	Time can also play a factor in Windows Solitaire, if the Timed game option is selected. For every 10 seconds of play, 2 points are taken away.
				<b><br><br>Notes On My Implementation</b><br><br>
				Drag cards to and from any stack. As long as the move is valid the card, or stack of 
				cards, will be repositioned in the desired spot. The game follows the standard scoring and time
				model explained above with only one waste card shown at a time.
				<p> The timer starts running as soon as 
				the game begins, but it may be paused by pressing the pause button at the bottom of
				the screen. 
		]]>
		</Rules>
		<Stack type="Draw" xpos="5" ypos="5" drawToStackID="1" shape="Stack" drawCount="3" drawToID="waste1"/>

		<Stack type="Waste" id="waste1" xpos="125" ypos="5" shape="Stack" />

		<!--  Foundations are defined for each suit.  Each one is defined as starting out empty, and specifies the first card that can be played on it.
				The firstCard examples here represent "Ace of any suit".  This attribute would only be needed if initialCard is not empty.
		-->
		<Stack type="Foundation" xpos="355" ypos="5" initialCard="" firstCard="A*" lockCards="1" shape="Stack" />
		<Stack type="Foundation" xpos="470" ypos="5" initialCard="" firstCard="A*" lockCards="1" shape="Stack" />
		<Stack type="Foundation" xpos="585" ypos="5" initialCard="" firstCard="A*" lockCards="1" shape="Stack" />
		<Stack type="Foundation" xpos="700" ypos="5" initialCard="" firstCard="A*" lockCards="1" shape="Stack" />
		
		<!--  Tab, or tableau,  Can have varying card counts.  
			Orientation:  Whether cards placed face up or down.  'DownTopUp' means all are face down, except the top card.
			splayed refers to how the cards are fanned out, the defined position being that of the first card.   
		-->
		<Stack type="Tab" xpos="10" ypos="200" cardCount="1" initFaceDown="0" shape="FanDown" firstCard="K*" lockCards="0"/>
		<Stack type="Tab" xpos="125" ypos="200" cardCount="2" initFaceDown="1" shape="FanDown" firstCard="K*" lockCards="0"/>
		<Stack type="Tab" xpos="240" ypos="200" cardCount="3" initFaceDown="2" shape="FanDown" firstCard="K*" lockCards="0"/>
		<Stack type="Tab" xpos="355" ypos="200" cardCount="4" initFaceDown="3" shape="FanDown" firstCard="K*" lockCards="0"/>
		<Stack type="Tab" xpos="470" ypos="200" cardCount="5" initFaceDown="4" shape="FanDown" firstCard="K*" lockCards="0"/>
		<Stack type="Tab" xpos="585" ypos="200" cardCount="6" initFaceDown="5" shape="FanDown" firstCard="K*" lockCards="0"/>
		<Stack type="Tab" xpos="700" ypos="200" cardCount="7" initFaceDown="6" shape="FanDown" firstCard="K*" lockCards="0"/>
	
		
		
	</Board>
	<MoveRules>
		<MoveRule destType="Foundation" cardSequence="Up" suitRequirement="SAME" allowGroup="0"/>
		<MoveRule destType="Tab" cardSequence="Down" suitRequirement="ALTCOLOR" allowGroup="1"/>
	</MoveRules>
</GameFile>


